# Larissa Huang

DATA SCIENTIST

lari.huang@gmail.com <u>GitHub</u> | <u>LinkedIn</u>

#### **PROFILE**

Blending a creative education with 4 years' experience as a developer, my journey into data science was sparked by a fascination with how data-driven insights can transform industries and solve complex problems. I bring a synthesis of programmatic skills and strategic acumen to any data science role.

#### **DATA SCIENCE SKILLS**

Python, SQL, R, Hypothesis Testing, Tableau, Matplotlib, Plotly, Bokeh, Seaborn, Machine Learning, SKLearn, Tensorflow, Keras, Pytorch, AWS, Hadoop, Spark, Hive, Docker

#### **DEVELOPMENT SKILLS**

React, JavaScript, TypeScript, Git, HTML & CSS, Agile, Responsive Web Development

#### **EDUCATION**

## BrainStation | Diploma, Data Science

JAN 2024 - APR 2024, VANCOUVER

## BCIT | New Media Design & Web Development

SEP 2017 - MAY 2018, VANCOUVER Graduated with distinction

## University of Wales | Bachelors in Creative Writing

SEP 2012 - JUNE 2016, WALES Graduated with first class honours

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Front End Developer | Engine Digital

JAN 2022 - MAR 2023, VANCOUVER, BC

- Developed award-winning, responsive digital projects for clients in diverse sectors with a focus on performance, security, and scalability.
- Assisted in a web overhaul for Prevalent, a cybersecurity client, significantly improving their web presence and contributing to their recognition as a representative vendor in Gartner's Market Guide.

### Software Developer | Epoch

APR 2021 - JAN 2022, VANCOUVER, BC

- Spearheaded time zone conversions for virtual events, extending the platform's reach to a global audience.
- Actively contributed to the design and development of a role-based dashboard with distinct user roles and custom features for each access level, aiding Epoch in securing clients such as StackOverflow, Udemy, and Reddit.

### Front End Developer | Engine Digital

SEP 2019 - APR 2021, VANCOUVER, BC

- Assisted in site architecture redesign and rebuild for Concord
   Theatricals\_after a major acquisition, working with extreme caution to integrate legacy code with new.
- Worked to develop an educational content portal for Power Smart for Schools, enabling over 250 teachers and students to access a suite of, energy-related, multimedia educational content during the pandemic.
- Worked on Engine Digital's agency website, with a focus on web animations and custom CMS development using Storyblok.

### Web Developer | O2E Brands

JUN - AUG 2019, VANCOUVER, BC

 Worked on integrating ArcGIS for search and geocoding for 1-800-GOT-JUNK's online booking engine, enabling users to easily find the closest franchise location on a map. In 2019, this booking engine saw over 40,000 bookings monthly.

#### **PROJECTS**

# BrainStation Capstone Project | Duck Duck Choose: Pecking at Pixels with Machine Learning

Using CNNs and Transfer Learning to Classify Images of Birds into Genus

## BrainStation Industry Project | GreenLoop: A Circular Economy POS Solution for Lush

Leveraging data on ecommerce customer preferences to propose personalized and unified ecommerce solutions for Lush